# Akshay Jogi

# Software Engineer

Focused and quick-learning with a positive "can-do" attitude Full Stack developer having around 6 years of experience in programming for various projects having good understanding of database, Node js, React, JavaScript, PHP Laravel, MVC pattern and object-oriented Concepts. Known for ability to work with team and individual, analysts and QA throughout the product life cycle to produce well tested, scalable and quality code.

akshay.b.jogi@gmail.com



9669290301



Chhindwara, India



in linkedin.com/in/akshay-jogi-b74822140

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# Sr. Software Engineer Santophy Infotech Pvt. Ltd.

06/2021 - 11/2023

Indore, India

Responsibilities

- Developed and maintained end-to-end web applications using a tech stack that included JavaScript, React, Node.js and REST apis.
- Independently developed and maintained web applications, taking ownership of the entire development lifecycle.
- Integrated third-party APIs and services and database design, including schema creation and optimisation.

# **Associate Software Engineer** Ksolves India Ltd

01/2020 - 12/2020

Indore, India

Responsibilities

- Participated in Agile development sprints, delivering incremental updates and features.
- Created the learning widget in multiple platforms like Microsoft Teams, Facebook workplace using React and Node js.
- Debugged and bug fixes to improve functionality and optimised components for maximum performance across a vast array of web-capable devices and browsers.

## **Associate Software Engineer** Codiant Software Technologies Pvt. Ltd

08/2017 - 12/2019

Responsibilities

- Collaborated with senior developers in the design and development of web applications using the Node js and Laravel PHP framework.
- Worked closely with cross-functional teams to gather requirements and provide technical support as needed.
- Implemented RESTful APIs to enable seamless data exchange with mobile team and integrating payment gateways.

## **EDUCATION**

## **Bachelor of Engineering in Computer** Science

Vindhya Institute Of Technology and Science

07/2017 - 05/2017

Indore, India

# Polytechnic Diploma in Information **Technology**

Govt. Polytechnic College, Ujjain

07/2011 - 05/2014 Ujjain, India

# **SKILLS**



## **PROJECTS**

#### Ekmatra

- Link: https://ekmatra.store
- Ek Matra is a unique one-stop platform for all corporate gifting supplies. They have integrated Zoho as their CRM.
- Technology Used: Node.js, Mysql, Angular.

#### Keep Me Posted

- Link: https://kmp-client.firebaseapp.com
- Keeps Me Posted provide facility to connect families and photos and text into a good old fashioned picture postcard, sent regularly to grandparents by post.
- Technology Used : Node js, React , Mongo DB, Firebase.

### EdCast

- Link https://services.edcast.ai
- EdCast offers a unified learning experience platform designed to enable end-to-end employee journeys spanning learning, skilling, and career mobility.
- Technology Used : Node js, React , Mongo DB.

#### Free Agent Football

- Link: https://www.freeagentfootball.com
- FreeAgentFootball is an advanced scouting and networking Platform for all individuals involved in the sport of football on all
- Technology Used: Node js, Laravel, Mysql.

#### CoverCrow

- Link: https://www.covercrow.com
- CoverCrow it is a cloud-based, on-demand job-calendaring system designed specifically for legal service professionals match court reporting freelancers with court reporting agencies.
- Technology Used: Vue.js, REST APIs, Laravel, PostgreSQL.

#### **ACHIEVEMENTS**

Legacy Leader Award - (08/2023)

Employee Of The Year Award - (08/2022)